(Amy:)It doesn't matter.
The element was found because of you,
(Amy:)and that's groundbreaking.
(Sheldon:)What matters is
the greatest scientific achievement
(Sheldon:)of my life is based on a blunder.
(Sheldon:)I'm not a genius, I'm a fraud.
(Amy:)You know, Sheldon, in neuroscience,
(Amy:)we're forever finding something
in one part of the brain
(Amy:)that we thought was some-place else.
(Sheldon:)Great. Now I'm worse than
a fraud. I'm practically a biologist.
You got to stop beating
yourself up over this.
I mean, you made a mistake,
but it was a happy mistake.
(Sheldon:)There's nothing happy about it.
(Sheldon:)I'm being given credit
that I don't deserve.
(Leonard:)People get things
they don't deserve all the time.
(Leonard:)Look at me with you.
(Sheldon:)No, Leonard, this is going
(Sheldon:)every science classroom, every
periodic table, every textbook.
(Sheldon:)This mistake
will be staring back at me
(Sheldon:)Like that time you let Koothrappali
wax your eyebrows.